



AMIR MABOOD

Nationality: Iranian (+90) 5546405389 **Date of birth:** 04/07/1997

Email address: amirmabood94040@gmail.com

Skype: https://join.skype.com/invite/Lct1pOiVe5Xz

Whatsapp Messenger: https://wa.me/+905528819139

in LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/amir-mabood

• Address: Antalya , Antalya hurma , ottman residence ii, 17402 antalya (Turkey)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Node is Developer

Sahar company [01/01/2019 - 01/01/2021]

City: tehran
Country: Iran

- We were a company with 20 developers and developing web sites like online-shop for customers in IRAN I have worked 2 years there as back-end developer.
- The main technologies that I've used are node.is , graphQL , MongoDB , PM2 , Git and Docker.

Mathematics teacher secondary school

Physic teacher in Salam High School [01/05/2018 - 01/05/2020]

City: tehran Country: Iran

- I was teacher in one of the top schools in Tehran as a Physic teacher for 2 years and I had 60 students every year .
- It was good experience to manage my students and help them to grow.
- We were able to increase the GPA by 20% in this course

Telegram Bot Developer

[01/01/2021 - 01/01/2022]

City: tehran **Country:** Iran

- I built telegram bot for edit combos in PSN market .Clients uploaded their combo txt file and after 3 minutes my bot editing their combo file automatic and sent them after rename file as {username}.txt
- This bot just accepted txt file limited and was selling monthly license to clients to edit their files as well as original file
- The main technologies that I've used are node.js , Telegraf

fullstack development (focus on backend)

Nasa-Project-Practice [01/01/2022 – 01/03/2022]

City: Antalya Country: Turkey

- I built a full-stack project where users are able to select their Destination Exoplanet , Rocket type , Mission Name and Launch Date then launch their mission.
- I was able to create Rocket types with parse CSV file in node.js and save it in database before server is running.
 Upcoming tab in this project is for check launches and delete them Then you can check deleted launches in history tab with red label This project has sound effects too and was able to use PM2 for handle requests well.
- $\,^\circ\,$ The main technologies that I've used are React , Node.js , MongoDB and Docker .

Pong-game

[01/04/2022 - 01/06/2022]

City: Antalya
Country: Turkey

- I provided a full-stack project (focus on back-end) where 2 users can play Pong game each other with socket.io.
- I was able to create socket.io server on node js and client side which allows users to play each other in rooms. and run express js side by side too. .
- The main technologies that I've used are socket.io , node js , express.js .

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

MongoDB for JavaScript Developers

MongoDB Online University [08/2022 - 09/2022]

Complete Node.js Development in 2022

Zero to Mastery Online University [2022]

Node.js Development

Freecodecamp Online University [2022]

Bachelor of Civil engineering

Tehran Azad University [2014 - 2018]

SUMMARY

node is / backend developer

Node.js web developer and network engineer seeking back-end developer role. Over 2 years of experience building back-end components and connecting applications to web-based services. High competencies in back-end JavaScript components, database systems and DevOps processes.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Persian

Other language(s):

English Italian

LISTENING B2 READING C1 WRITING C1 LISTENING A2 READING B1 WRITING B1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2 SPOKEN PRODUCTION A2 SPOKEN INTERACTION A2

DIGITAL SKILLS

My Digital Skills

Backend Development / node js / expressjs / Docker Container / Git + Github + Subversion / Web API (RESTful, GraphQL) / Restful APIs / AWS Web Services / Javascript ES6 / Typescript / Databases, SQL and NoSQL / Authentication / DenoJs / SocketIO / Node.js Tests with(Jest, Supertest)